http://www.omniupdate.com/company/policies/privacy.html

By continuing to use this site, you agree to the storing of first- and third-party
cookies on your device to enhance site navigation; analyze site, product, and service
usage; and assist in our marketing and promotional efforts. Cookie Policy
Agree
If you see this don't fill out this input box.
Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
OmniUpdate is deeply committed to user privacy and to the security of all data in
our possession. The following privacy policy is meant to help you understand what
information we collect, why we collect it, and how you can update, manage, and delete
your information.
Information Collection
Personal information collection when you visit our websites, use OU Campus, and/or
use OmniUpdate developed products
Personal information refers to any information that you voluntarily submit to us that
identifies you personally, including contact information such as your name, email
address, phone number, company name, address, and any other information about your
business or yourself. Personal information can also include information about you
that is available on the internet, such as from Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, and Google,
or publicly available information that we acquire from service providers.
OmniUpdate.com, OU Campus, and OmniUpdate developed products utilize Google Analytics
and other tools to track and analyze internet visitor usage data, which may include
your IP address, geographical location, browser type, domain name(s), internet service
provider (ISP), the pages and files viewed on our site, operating system, length of
visit, access times, referring website addresses, and web browser cookies. We also
may utilize third parties to target advertisements to visitor interest categories.
This information is used by OmniUpdate to operate and improve our website, products,
and services; to personalize information; and to provide general statistics regarding
use and user behavior so that we can continually improve them. In some cases, we do
link this automatically-collected data to personal information voluntarily submitted
such as name, email address, address, and phone number.
If credit card information is collected to secure payment for services, such information
is not stored by OmniUpdate. Our bank assists in the processing of credit card transactions
and all card information is destroyed after the transaction is successfully completed.
Payments made via check are processed through private bank means and all checking
information is maintained securely in our office and with our bank. Billing information
is never used by OmniUpdate for marketing or promotional purposes.
Cookies
We use cookies when you visit our websites, use OU Campus, and/or use other OmniUpdate
developed products to help us provide you with a good browsing and user experience
and it also allows us to improve our site, products, and services. By continuing to
browse the site, use OU Campus, and/or use other OmniUpdate developed products, you
are agreeing to our use of cookies.
A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the
hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your
computer’s hard drive.
We use the following cookies:
Strictly necessary cookies. These are cookies that are required for the operation of our website. They include,
for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website or make
use of our products and services.
Analytical/performance cookies. They allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors
move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our
website works, for example, by ensuring that users find what they are looking for
easily.
Functionality cookies. These are used to recognize you when you return to our website. This enables us to
personalize our content for you, greet you by name, and remember your preferences
(for example, your choice of language or region).
Targeting cookies. These cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited, and the
links you have followed. We will use this information to make our website and the
advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this
information with third parties for this purpose.
You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes
for which we use them below.
Third-party cookies
Our websites, products, and services will set several types of third-party cookies,
and we do not control the operation of any of them. The third-party cookies that may
be set include:
Google Analytics – We use Google Analytics to collect data about website usage. This
data does not include personally identifiable information. View the Google Privacy Policy.
Google Remarketing – We use Google’s Remarketing cookie to market products and services
we think may be of interest to you. You may see our adverts on Google’s Display Advertising
Network of partner websites and Google’s own search results pages. We aim to carefully
select the products and services we remarket to you and do so based on the pages you
have visited on our website. To opt out of Google Remarketing, set your Google Ad Settings.
Zendesk, Inc. – This license cookie enables our installation of Zendesk, making it
possible for visitors to use the support chat functionality on our support site. It
does not collect any personally identifiable information. Read the Zendesk Privacy Policy.
LiveChat, Inc. – This license cookie enables our installation of LiveChat, making
it possible for visitors to use the LiveChat functionality on this site. It does not
automatically collect any personally identifiable information. Read the LiveChat Privacy Policy.
Salesforce Pardot – Pardot tracks visitor and prospect activities on our website and
landing pages. Pardot cookies don’t store personally identifying information, only
a unique identifier. Read the Salesforce Pardot Privacy Policy.
VisualVisitor – We use VisualVisitor’s website analytics and tracking tool. This includes
collection of IP address, navigational patterns, and placement of two cookies that
associate website activity with a device linking sessions and visits. Read the VisualVisitor Privacy Policy.
Triblio – We use Triblio’s platform to collect data about website usage and to personalize
our website. This includes collection of IP address, navigational patterns, and placement
of cookies to market products and services that may be of interest to you. Read the
Triblio Privacy Policy.
FullStory – OmniUpdate uses FullStory to track and understand user behavior within
beta and demo environments in service to improving the customer experience. OmniUpdate
employees engaged in the design and development of OU Campus can see a rendering of
the path the user has taken through the product. FullStory captures your OU Campus
user name, full name, gravitar image, IP address, and IP-based geolocation. Where
possible, OmniUpdate uses functionality that will blur user data so that employees
cannot see it as they watch the FullStory reproductions of the user’s experience.
However, the messaging and notifications feature does not support blurring of data,
so it is advised that users refrain from including sensitive or personally identifiable
data within the subject or body of the messages. Read the FullStory Privacy Policy.
Typeform - OmniUpdate uses a forms tool provided by Typeform to survey our customers for feedback
related to improving our products and services. We will never ask for personal information
not directly related to the topic on which we’re soliciting feedback, but we often
ask for the customer’s name and school affiliation. Additionally, we receive the user’s
IP address in the response to the surveys.  Read the Typeform Privacy and Cookie Policies.
UserVoice - OmniUpdate uses services provided by UserVoice to support our support
chat capabilities. To learn more about the data that UserVoice collects and how they
use it, read the UserVoice Privacy Policy.
SocialEngine - OmniUpdate uses services provided by SocialEngine to support our OmniUpdate
Community Network discussion forum that enables our customers to suggest enhancements
to OU Campus, vote on the suggestions, and get support from OmniUpdate and peers. To
learn more about the data that SocialEngine collects and how they use it, read the
SocialEngine Privacy Policy.
You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to
refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings
to block all cookies you may not be able to access all or parts of our sites.
Information we collect from third parties
From time to time, we may receive personal information about you from third-party
sources, including partners with which we offer co-branded services or engage in joint
marketing activities and publicly available sources such as social media websites.
Information about children
Our websites are not intended for or targeted to children under 16 years of age, and
we do not knowingly or intentionally collect information about children under 16 years
of age. If you believe that we have collected information about a child under 16 years
of age, please contact us at marketing@omniupdate.com so that we may delete the information.
Do not track
Some internet browsers include the ability to transmit “Do Not Track” signals. Since
uniform standards for “Do Not Track” signals have not been adopted, OmniUpdate websites
do not currently process or respond to “Do Not Track” signals. To learn more about
“Do Not Track,” please visit All About Do Not Track.
Information Use
We use the information we collect only in compliance with this Privacy Policy. We will never sell your personal information to any third party.
In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may use your
personal information to:
Improve your browsing experience by personalizing our websites and/or to improve our
services and products
Send information or content to you that we think may be of interest to you by post,
email, or other means
Send you marketing communications relating to our business, products, or services
Promote use of our services to you and share promotional and information content with
you in accordance with your communication preferences
Provide other companies with statistical information (not personally identifiable)
about our users
Send information to you regarding changes to our Privacy Policy or other legal agreements
Meet legal requirements
We may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about
a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, we do not transfer
your personal information to the third party.
We use the information collected through our services by our customers for the following
purposes:
To provide products or services (which may include the detection, prevention, and
resolution of security and technical issues)
To respond to customer support requests
To fulfill the obligations under our Customer Terms of Service
Customer testimonials and comments
We post customer testimonials and comments on our websites that may contain personal
information. We obtain each customer's consent via email prior to posting the customer's
name and testimonial. On our support site, we have several forms asking for your feedback
on training sessions and support materials. Information provided in these surveys
is used to improve our training curriculum and support materials. These surveys may
ask you for personal information; you can choose whether or not to volunteer that
information.
Retention of personal information
How long we keep information we collect about you depends on the type of information,
as described in further detail below.  After such time, we will either delete or anonymize
your information or, if this is not possible, we will securely store your information
and isolate it from any further use until deletion is possible.
We retain personal information that you provide to us where we have an ongoing legitimate
business need to do so (for example, as long as is required in order to contact you
about our products or services, or as needed to comply with our legal obligations,
resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements).
When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information,
we securely delete the information or anonymize it or, if this is not possible, we
will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing
until deletion is possible. We will delete this information from the servers at an
earlier date if you so request, as described in the Opt-Out section below.
If you have elected to receive marketing communications from us, we retain information
about your marketing preferences for a reasonable period of time from the date you
last expressed interest in our content, products, or services, such as when you last
opened an email from us or ceased using your OmniUpdate account. We retain information
derived from cookies and other tracking technologies for a reasonable period of time
from the date such information was created.
Information Sharing
Service providers
We employ other companies and people to provide services to visitors to our websites,
our customers, and users of our products and/or services and may need to share your
information with them to provide information, products, or services to you. Examples
may include removing repetitive information from prospect lists, analyzing data or
performing statistical analysis, providing marketing assistance, processing credit
card payments, supplementing the information you provide us in order to provide you
with better service, and providing customer service or support. In all cases where
we share your information with such agents, we explicitly require the agent to acknowledge
and adhere to our privacy and customer data handling policies.
OmniUpdate partners
In addition, we may share data with trusted partners to contact you based on your
request to receive such communications, help us perform statistical analysis, or provide
customer support. Such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information
except for these purposes, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of
your information.
We partner with trusted third parties to provide you with co-marketing content that
we think may be relevant to you. When you engage with these co-marketing partners,
we will tell you who we are sharing data with and provide a link to the co-marketing
partner’s privacy policy so you can learn more about how to opt out of the partner’s
communications. These co-marketing partners are required to adhere to our privacy
and data protection policies. Learn more about our co-marketing program.
Compelled disclosure
We reserve the right to use or disclose your personal information if required by law
or if we reasonably believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect our rights,
protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or comply with a law,
court order, or legal process.
Information Security
The OmniUpdate network has extensive protective measures in place to ensure that misuse,
loss, corruption, and alteration of data does not happen. To ensure the continued
security of your individualized information, OmniUpdate conducts periodic reviews
of our security infrastructure, regularly updating our practices to meet the highest
technological and data protection industry standards. We protect unauthorized access
and inappropriate use of sensitive data at both the hardware and software levels,
including the use of properly configured network firewalls, Secure Socket Layers (SSL),
and VPN technologies for data in transit and encryption for data storage. Our products
also incorporate advanced security features and methods, including encoded session
identifications and dynamic data. The OmniUpdate team is also committed to internal
policies that dictate exactly how employees may use and access secure data.
OmniUpdate does not share, distribute, print, or reference any individualized information
except as may be required by law. We will only view or access individual information
with specific permission as needed to implement products and services or to resolve
a support issue. However, users may elect to share such information with a third-party
vendor to perform certain specific services deemed reputable and secure by OmniUpdate
management. Please note that each user is responsible for maintaining the security
of their own email accounts and OU Campus user credentials, including passwords.
Opt-Out Policy
We want to make sure you are comfortable with the way we use your information and
know how to change your preferences. As an OmniUpdate customer, please note that you
have the right to decide how we use the information you provide to us. Should you
wish to opt out of receiving general marketing information or to request deletion
of your data, please send us an email request detailing your preferred level of contact
and/or request for deletion of data. Send your request to marketing@omniupdate.com and we will remove your information from our contact lists and/or database(s).
You may opt out of Google's Display Advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings page. You also may be interested in viewing the Consumer Opt-Out page for the Network Advertising Initiative to opt out of other participating networks.
You may opt out of FullStory's analytic and error tracking by visiting fullstory.com/optout/.
Links to External Websites
OmniUpdate websites may contain links to other websites. OmniUpdate is not responsible
for the content of these websites or for their respective privacy policies. Customers
should carefully read and consider the privacy policy of such sites before disclosing
any individualized information.
Concerns or Changes
OmniUpdate may change this privacy policy at any time by posting revisions to this
website. Your use of this website constitutes acceptance of the provisions of this
privacy policy and your continued usage after such changes are posted constitutes
acceptance of each revised policy policy. Please check this privacy policy periodically
for changes. If you do not agree to the terms of this privacy policy or any revised
privacy policy, please exit the website immediately. Should you have any concerns
or questions regarding this policy, please contact OmniUpdate Marketing at marketing@omniupdate.com.
Contact
OmniUpdate1320 Flynn Rd., Ste. 100Camarillo, CA 93012
Updated: September 11, 2019
Stay Connected
Get announcements straight to your inbox about our free webcasts, upcoming events, product updates, and more!
Join our mailing list to stay connected!
Subscribe now
Join our mailing list to stay connected!
Get announcements straight to your inbox about new blog posts, free webcasts, upcoming
events, and more.
